# **ANDREY VERZIN**

Yalta, Gurzuf, Solovieva st., 12-28, 298640 Crimea +79789909937 Artecovec@gmail.com

artecovec.github.io/ in ru.linkedin.com/in/avfrontender



# Front end Developer

### Summary

Hi, I'm advanced Web Developer with over 4 years experience in structuring, coding and developing interactive websites. Able to create own projects or understand others developers code and work with it. Well-qualified to create attractive user-friendly websites. Organized and disciplined to make projects in time. Enjoy team work.

#### Skills

Good knowledge of - HTML5, CSS3, SASS (SCSS), native JavaScript, JQuery

I use - Grunt, Photoshop, Bootstrap, Git, Foundation, Angular

I am familar with - OOP, Python, Compass

## Work History

May 2017 - Present

Engineer - programmer

ICC "Artek"

- Installation and maintenance of software
- administration of computer network
- ip phone and ip-camera maintenance
- windows server administration

Jul 2014 - Mar 2017

Frontend developer

Brightside

- Develop and code responsible websites and landing pages.
- Manage web projects with 2-4 developers
- Increase website production to 35%

Sep 2008 - Jun 2014

Engineer-programmer

"SpecGaz" LLC

- Installed and maintained software
- Administrated computer network
- Developed software on Delphi

Education

07.2019 - 10.2019

Programmer

**ISTIM** 

IT Technologies and automatization

2003 - 2008

Specialist

Kursk State University

IT Technologies and English

——————————————————————————————————————					
Several examples of my w	orks:				
brightlanding.ru	ultramar.lv	wilbo.ru	fkr.ru	sfera.fm	

Created with **TVisualCV**